customerkart.com 2017-11-18

# Privacy Policy –customerkarts.com - Customer Care Number

**Privacy Policy**

Your privacy is Important and primary aim of our team. It’s our job to shield your privacy and private info. We have a tendency to respect your personal info and we offer our commitment that we will never misuse your personal details and privacy.

We may collect non-personal identification data concerning Users whenever they interrelate with our web site like browser name, type of computer and technical data concerning Users and other similar details. Our team will assure you that we will never reveal or disclose your info with 3rd party.

 **Google Adsense and Web Browser Cookies**

Our website might use “cookies” to reinforce User expertise. User’s web browser places cookies on their disk drive for record-keeping point of view and generally to trace info regarding them. User may select to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to warn you once cookies are being sent.

Google, as a 3rd party advertisement marketer, uses cookies to serve ads on this web site. customerkarts.com has no access or management over these cookies which will be employed by third party advertisers.

 **How We Protect Your Information**

We adopt acceptable data collection, storage and process practices and security measures to shield against unconstitutional access, amendment, destruction of your personal info, username, password, transaction info and details stored on our website.

We don’t sell, trade, or rent Users personal identification info to others. We may share basic collective demographic details not joined to any personal identification info concerning users with our business partners, trusty affiliates and advertisers.

 **Changes to This Privacy Policy**

Customers Forum has discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we’ll revise the updated date at the lowest part of this page. We advised to all Users to often check this page for any amendment or modification to remain aware about how we are serving to protect the private data we collect from users. You acknowledge and agree that it’s your liability to evaluate this privacy policy sporadically and become awake to modifications.

 **Your Acceptance of These Terms**

By using this Site, you show your acceptance of this policy. If you do not concur to this policy, please do not use our web portal. Your use of this portal following the posting of changes to the present policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.

 **Links to Third Party Websites**

We have enclosed links on this web portal for your use and reference. We are not accountable for the privacy policies on these websites. You should be remembered that the privacy policies of those sites might be different from our own.

 **Contact Us**

If you have any query about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us at customerkart@yahoo.com.
